https://www.finewinehouse.com/privacy-policy/

Created with Sketch.
Created with Sketch.
Jim Beam
Old Forester Birthday Bourbon Kentucky Straight Bourbon Whisky 750ml
Privacy Policy
We believe in your right to privacy. What information do we gather? How do we use it? When you place an order, FineWineHouse needs to know your full name, credit card number and expiration date as they appear on the credit card. We also need your billing address, shipping address, home phone number and email address. This information allows to fill your order, contact you regarding your order, and ship your order to you. Protecting your information When an order is placed at ShopWineDirect, we use a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you enter into the form before it sends it to us.
By displaying the Secure Certificate, FineWineHouse has agreed to notify users of:
1.What personally identifiable information FineWineHouse collects.
2.What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the Web site.
3.What organization collects the information.
4.How FineWineHouse uses the information.
5.With whom FineWineHouse may share user information.
6.What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.
7.What measures FineWineHouset takes to protect the information under its control.
8.How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Disclosure of Personal Information FineWineHouse will not sell, trade or rent personal information about our customers or visitors to others. We will never willfully disclose any information about any of our customers to any third party without first receiving that individuals permission.
×
Quick Links
Blog
Buy Wine Online
About Us
Contact
Customer Service
Privacy Policy
Connect with Us:
©
FineWineHouse
| Sitemap
